[Upbeat music playing]
[SCARY TONE!]
Lansing has been called by many, "Technically the capital of Michigan."
But there's more to our city than the government workers who flee the city boundaries promptly at 5:01.
Yes, that's right. Lansing residents - or Lanstranauts as they like to be called -
spend time each year touring the scenic, and baffling parking lots of Horrocks and Frandor.
[Car horn honking] AAAAAAAAHHHHHHHHHGGGGGHHHH
Lansing has the unique distinction of leading the nation in "Things that are other things."
A cell phone shop, that's also a barbecue restaurant. A gas station, that's a Cuban sandwich place.
A liquor store, that's also a laundromat. A baseball stadium that's also a soccer stadium.
A porn shop, that's also a psychic parlor. And by 2025: A city that's also a hospital!
[Magical sounds of Sparrow taking over the city]
How do I get out of here? Six hours... I've got to figure something out.
For those looking to make a home in Lansing, there are many vibrant neighborhoods to choose from.
Like the Eastside, it's got a restaurant now. Or downtown, a great place to get a sandwich... before 4:00 PM.
Or REO Town, home to one business per power plant. Old Town, like REO Town, but for Chase Sapphire members.
South Lansing, home to the world's premier Fast Food Architectural Preserve.
Whether you're looking to live. Work. Play. Just blast the Speedwagon.
[REO Speedwagon's "Keep on Loving you" blares from car speakers]
Lansing is a city that's gonna keep on loving you. It's 5:15... so....
[Upbeat music continues]